How are you going to reach your father?
Sagittarius star is under a total entertainment ban.
I may be the daughter of the Zodiac CEO,
but it's impossible for a member of Zero-Zero to move freely throughout the planet.
Okay, what's the plan?
Thank you, Yasunaga.
I'm just happy you're safe and sound, my lady.
Yasuguna has been serving the family since before I was even born.
Nice to meet you, Motomiya-sama.
Oh, it's nice to meet you as well.
So this is where Chiyeri was born.
Whoa.
Your house is incredible.
Really?
Miss, I shall do my very best to ensure you see your father.
Please relax in the meantime.
Very well.
Music
Aminiyaaran
Midayaaran
Midayaram
Visit
all
y
yeah
Thank you.
That's Sagittarius star?
How are we supposed to find Nagisa and Chieri down there?
It won't be easy.
I wonder if Chieri came back here to try and settle things with her father.
If so, she's being quite reckless.
Zodiac headquarters is like a fortress.
We're going to save them, right?
Tsubasa-san is doing her best to make a plan of action.
We'll have to wait a little longer.
Man, I hate this!
Is there really nothing we can do but sit around and wait?
The Woda Intelligence Corps are looking for a way into Sagittarius star.
Until they can find something, we're on our own.
So what are we going to do?
You're thinking about taking back Akibasta, right?
Mm-hmm.
I'm home.
Sorry for the intrusion.
This is your room?
Yes.
It's just the way I left it.
Not a thing has changed.
Chieri, is it okay if I wait here for a while?
It feels so nice.
It's been so long since I've been able to take a bath.
It will be some time until I can see my father.
I wonder when he'll show up.
Probably real late, huh?
He won't come here.
I still don't think he ever comes home.
He's always been that way.
He didn't come home when my mother died or when my brother died.
Why wouldn't he?
He's too busy with work.
I was always all alone in this huge house.
I was surrounded by helpers, tutors, and self-defense instructors.
They raised me.
Self-defense?
He wanted a healthy successor.
I was supposed to take over the company someday.
It must be hard work, being a rich girl.
Oh, wow!
I've never worn anything like this!
Are you sure I can borrow it, Chieri?
Yes.
I'm having someone wash our clothes.
Oh, right.
It's already gotten too tight.
It's so quiet.
It's like there's nobody here.
It's a cold city, isn't it?
This is what planets with total entertainment bans are like.
A total entertainment ban.
How did you find out about Zero-Zero?
In a way, it was thanks to my father.
My father forgot his tablet at home once.
I happened to see a Zero-Zero video he had there.
Even as a child, I vaguely sensed it was something forbidden.
But I had Yasunaga gather various Zero-Zero videos and songs for me in secret.
Then, as destiny would have it, that summer, my father took me with him on a site inspection.
And that was…
Yes.
It was Lancaster.
What's wrong?
Do you want to buy one, Lord?
We came to eat, too.
Do you want me to buy one for you?
It's hard when it's so crowded.
Sagittarius star?
Yeah.
Cool!
I've never met a kid from another planet before.
Me neither.
Yeah!
I've never eaten like this before.
It's good.
Nagisa and Murumiya, nice to meet you.
I'm Yuka Ichijo.
Orine Aira.
I'm Cherry Sono.
You were the first friends I'd ever made.
And you were the first person to tell us about AKB.
It really was destiny.
Mm-hmm.
You're absolutely certain?
Yes.
Just as you were informed, AKB-0048 intends to perform a guerrilla concert on Lancaster.
That was the first time I wanted to become a member of Zero-Zero.
Me, too.
But…
After the concert was over…
Akarara?
Chieri, did you go to the Zero-Zero concert?
I'm sorry, Father, but I…
I want to become a member of Zero-Zero.
Tell me, Chieri, did Karara glow in response to you?
What?
No, I don't think it did.
It's been dim since the concert ended.
I see.
Then you do not possess the glow.
Entertainment is forbidden.
And AKB-0048 is a group of unlawful terrorists.
Don't think of such pointless things.
You are my daughter.
You are the successor of the Zodiac Corporation.
Even after I returned to Sagittarius Star, I continued to plead with my father.
He never listened to me.
心のどこかに
ひとつ星がある
運命の人
住んでいると
教えられた
悲しい時には
天体望遠鏡を
空に向けて
また見えない
愛を探す
遥か彼方
誰かが
気が付いてくれたら
時を超えて
日常は
光のメッセージ
寂寺に行くと
暗に代わり
できてしまう
What does the CEO possibly want with me?
I just finished discussing the new Dualium Mining Plan.
Since it had your approval, I doubt that's the reason I'm here.
Both of us have daughters in AKB-0048.
I thought that we should meet.
Furthermore, I found the report you submitted to the Entertainment Administration Bureau.
The relationship between entertainment and work efficiency, quite interesting.
How do you know about that?
Planets which allow entertainment are found to have a higher labor efficiency rating
than those with even partial entertainment bands.
It was an interesting observation on your part.
It's the truth, grounded in hard-researched facts.
In other words, you believe we should free entertainment?
I think we should investigate the possibility, yes.
Look for the door that cannot be seen.
The secret stairs are right beside them.
First, oppression, then liberation.
And once that's happened,
well, we may have our very own wonderland.
I have one good memory with my father.
What is it?
After I sang in front of his room,
my father took me to bed when I fell asleep.
I still remember that warmth.
The next day when I asked Yasnagat,
he said he found me in the hallway and put me to bed.
But I knew...
I knew that my father was the one who carried me.
And if that's really the case...
Nagisa!
The Zodiac SP!
I'm sorry, Miss Chiari, but we must restrain the both of you for the time being.
What's going on?
It was your father's orders, ma'am.
Yasnagat!
I'm sorry, my lady, but I've kept my promise.
I will take you to see your father now.
The dualium crystals on that planet responded to the members
and strengthened the Kiraras in the process.
As fate would have it,
a massive quantity of dualium is buried beneath Akibastar.
We will warp underground using the Kirara drive
and create a reaction with the dualium.
Okay.
But can we really warp to a location with that much accuracy?
It's possible if we synchronize this crystal.
So we're gonna use the dualium crystal Orine got from the Fungis?
Even if we make it in,
there's no guarantee we can create a strong enough reaction.
It's impossible.
That is, unless all of you are able to achieve Centanova Class Glows
once we get started.
But then how are we supposed to do that?
That settles it. They're crazy.
Agreed. But it seems like something Nagisa would do.
Oh, totally. Chiari, too.
They're both off their rockers.
Maybe that's why the two of them shine so brightly.
You're right. They're always walking ahead of us.
Even if it's crazy or impossible,
they do what they can to make their dreams come true.
Pretty inspiring, isn't it?
You okay?
Yes, I'm fine. I just may have been overthinking things a little bit.
But can such reckless girls become the Centanova?
The Centanova?
I don't want to lose.
I don't want to lose to either of them.
Neither do I! I want to shine brighter than ever before!
The details of our plan to take back Akiba's star have been established.
I'll explain that …
Tsubasa-san!
Yukiri, what is it?
We've been contacted by Koji Haru on Akiba's star. Tsubasa-san!
Send it through the monitor.
Roger!
Hey there! Long time no see, ladies!
Good to see you!
Your father wishes to speak with you, Miss Chieri.
Hello, daughter.
What do you think you're doing?
Is that how a daughter should speak to her father at their reunion?
I think you'd at least be grateful for my protection.
I have watched everything you've done lately.
Honestly, I never imagined you had so much hidden talent.
You have begun to shine.
You made me popular because you recognized my potential.
In order to make me the Centanova and use me.
Use you?
Take a look.
The Flying Get!
They're waiting just outside Sagittarius Star's defensive line.
I can order a DES attack and finish them off for good.
No, don't!
There's no need for that.
I'll give you what you want.
Oh?
I will become the Centanova, okay?
Just promise that you won't hurt Nagisa or the rest of Zero Zero anymore!
What?
Very well.
Come.
Show me your shine, my daughter.
This is crazy, Chiarie! Don't go!
Nagisa, I want to thank you for everything.
I'm going to face him alone.
Wait!
Chiarie!
Kojiharu, meet up with Woda!
You can count on me!
Now it's just…
Nagisa and Chiarie!
You're…
Oh!
Nagisa's father?
What are you doing here?
You first.
Nagisa is fine.
I understand.
Thank you.
I'm jealous of Nagisa sometimes.
Her mother and father understand her.
We don't understand her, actually.
We didn't allow her to join AKB 0048.
Ah…
You see, we're simply walking along different paths.
The paths we believe in are different.
The paths you believe in?
No…
You believe in?
We may walk different paths, but in the end we are still a family.
That, that all there is to it.
Perhaps I should not say so.
But your father is a very lonely man.
Lonely?
My father?
He walks alone on the path he chose.
And…
I don't even think he realizes it.
My daughter will become the Sen intra-nova soon.
A power beyond that of even time and space.
Once that glow belongs to me alone,
I don't care what happens to entertainment.
His desire may be twisted.
However, it's obvious he wants someone to walk alongside him.
At least, that's how it seemed to me.
I'll go the rest of the way by myself.
As you wish, my lady.
Thank you.
Finally, we can begin.
Sigh.
Singled Produkt
Unfortunately, it didn't find me empty of love.
For the world, You got to go somewhere else.
In the sky, I'm not looking to see any large eternal lover.
愛を探す遥か彼方 誰かが気が付いてくれたら
時を越えていつかは辿り着く光のメッセージ
間違いなくここにいるよ 目を伏せてても
拒絶しているのじゃなく不器用なだけ
間違いなく待っているよ 忘れられても
偶然がきっと重なった時
あなたに会えるはず
いつまでだってここにいるよ 不安になっても
絶望しているのじゃなく夢は見てるよ
いつまでだって信じてるよ ひとりきいても
黄色とはまるで違う自分に
明日は生まれ変わる
この光が終わる
終わるのが終わる
間違いなくここにいるよ 目を伏せてても
拒絶しているのじゃなく不器用なだけ
間違いなく待っているよ 忘れられても
偶然がきっと重なった時
あなたに会えるはず
じゃいきたい人
キ proceeding
拒絶で安心のこと
前には消誊しているよ
お前には
It's my father! He's in trouble!
Father!
You mustn't touch him, my lady!
Let go of me! I have to help him!
The CEO has been shot!
Contact the police and army immediately!
Father!
I have to help him!
God bless her!
Thank you.
Two人が出会った頃 夢などまだ種だった
それくらい時が過ぎ 花は咲くのだろう
この涙を君に捧ぐ もっと君が輝くな
ずっと見守ってた 深奥の空から
今僕は雨になろう
Ah 君に捧ぐ こんな僕にできることは
君の虚しさを 少しでも癒すこと
さあ 僕は雨になろう
ご視聴ありがとうございました